 export const television = [
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20police%20officer%20in%20the%20cartoon%20%22Top%20Cat%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "Dibble",
     incorrect_answers: ["Barbrady", "Mahoney", "Murphy"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20TV%20show%20%22Cheers%22%2C%20Sam%20Malone%20was%20a%20former%20relief%20pitcher%20for%20which%20baseball%20team%3F",
     correct_answer: "Boston%20Red%20Sox",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "New%20York%20Mets",
       "Baltimore%20Orioles",
       "Milwaukee%20Brewers",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20TV%20show%20%27M%2AA%2AS%2AH%27%2C%20what%20was%20the%20nickname%20of%20Corporal%20Walter%20O%27Reilly%3F",
     correct_answer: "Radar",
     incorrect_answers: ["Hawkeye", "Hot%20Lips", "Trapper"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Who%20played%20Agent%20Fox%20Mulder%20in%20the%20TV%20sci-fi%20drama%20%22The%20X-Files%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "David%20Duchovny",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Gillian%20Anderson",
       "Robert%20Patrick",
       "Mitch%20Pileggi",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Who%20is%20the%20star%20of%20the%20AMC%20series%20Breaking%20Bad%3F",
     correct_answer: "Walter%20White",
     incorrect_answers: ["Saul%20Goodman", "Jesse%20Pinkman", "Skyler%20White"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20original%20Star%20Trek%20TV%20series%2C%20what%20was%20Captain%20James%20T.%20Kirk%27s%20middle%20name%3F",
     correct_answer: "Tiberius",
     incorrect_answers: ["Trevor", "Travis", "Tyrone"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Grant%20Gustin%20plays%20which%20superhero%20on%20the%20CW%20show%20of%20the%20same%20name%3F",
     correct_answer: "The%20Flash",
     incorrect_answers: ["The%20Arrow", "Black%20Canary", "Daredevil"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20which%20British%20seaside%20town%20was%20the%20BBC%20sitcom%20%22Fawlty%20Towers%22%20set%3F",
     correct_answer: "Torquay",
     incorrect_answers: ["Blackpool", "Bournemouth", "Great%20Yarmouth"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20these%20Bojack%20Horseman%20characters%20is%20a%20human%3F",
     correct_answer: "Todd%20Chavez",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Lennie%20Turtletaub",
       "Princess%20Carolyn",
       "Tom%20Jumbo-Grumbo",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20these%20characters%20in%20%22Stranger%20Things%22%20has%20the%20power%20of%20Telekinesis%3F",
     correct_answer: "Eleven",
     incorrect_answers: ["Mike", "Lucas", "Karen"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20show%20Stranger%20Things%2C%20what%20is%20Eleven%27s%20favorite%20breakfast%20food%3F",
     correct_answer: "Eggo%20Waffles",
     incorrect_answers: ["Toast", "Captain%20Crunch", "Bacon%20and%20Eggs"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20show%2C%20Doctor%20Who%2C%20what%20does%20T.A.R.D.I.S%20stand%20for%3F",
     correct_answer: "Time%20And%20Relative%20Dimensions%20In%20Space",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Time%20And%20Resting%20Dimensions%20In%20Space",
       "Time%20And%20Relative%20Dimensions%20In%20Style",
       "Toilet%20Aid%20Rope%20Dog%20Is%20Soup",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Guy%27s%20Grocery%20Games%20is%20hosted%20by%20which%20presenter%3F",
     correct_answer: "Guy%20Fieri",
     incorrect_answers: ["Guy%20Martin", "Guy%20Ritchie", "Ainsley%20Harriott"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "The%20%22Psycho%22%20series%20of%20videos%20on%20YouTube%20was%20created%20by%20which%20of%20the%20following%3F",
     correct_answer: "RiDGiD%20STUDiOS",
     incorrect_answers: ["Dan%20Bell", "Billy%20Familia", "VeganGainz"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "How%20many%20seasons%20did%20%22Stargate%20SG-1%22%20have%3F",
     correct_answer: "10",
     incorrect_answers: ["3", "7", "12"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Who%20is%20the%20main%20character%20in%20the%20show%20%22Burn%20Notice%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "Michael%20Westen",
     incorrect_answers: ["Sam%20Axe", "Fiona%20Glenanne", "Madeline%20Westen"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20company%20has%20exclusive%20rights%20to%20air%20episodes%20of%20the%20%22The%20Grand%20Tour%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "Amazon",
     incorrect_answers: ["Netflix", "BBC", "CCTV"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20Star%20Trek%20universe%2C%20what%20color%20is%20Vulcan%20blood%3F",
     correct_answer: "Green",
     incorrect_answers: ["Blue", "Red", "Purple"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20country%20is%20Cory%20in%20the%20House%20set%20in%3F",
     correct_answer: "The%20United%20States%20of%20America",
     incorrect_answers: ["Canada", "Venezuala", "England"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20Game%20of%20Thrones%2C%20what%20continent%20lies%20across%20the%20Narrow%20Sea%20from%20Westeros%3F",
     correct_answer: "Essos",
     incorrect_answers: ["Easteros", "Westereast", "Esuntos"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20Game%20of%20Thrones%2C%20what%20is%20Littlefinger%27s%20real%20name%3F",
     correct_answer: "Petyr%20Baelish",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Podrick%20Payne",
       "Lancel%20Lannister",
       "Torrhen%20Karstark",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "When%20did%20the%20TV%20show%20Rick%20and%20Morty%20first%20air%20on%20Adult%20Swim%3F",
     correct_answer: "2013",
     incorrect_answers: ["2014", "2016", "2015"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20Supernatural%2C%20what%27s%20is%20Sam%27s%20brothers%20name%3F",
     correct_answer: "Dean",
     incorrect_answers: ["Dave", "Steve", "Mike"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20DuckTales%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20city%20where%20all%20the%20main%20characters%20live%3F",
     correct_answer: "Duckburg",
     incorrect_answers: ["Duckwing", "Tailspin", "Wingford"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20television%20show%20Breaking%20Bad%2C%20what%20is%20the%20street%20name%20of%20Walter%20and%20Jesse%27s%20notorious%20product%3F",
     correct_answer: "Blue%20Sky",
     incorrect_answers: ["Baby%20Blue", "Rock%20Candy", "Pure%20Glass"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20the%20first%20episode%20of%20Doctor%20Who%20to%20air%20in%201963%3F",
     correct_answer: "An%20Unearthly%20Child",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "The%20Daleks",
       "The%20Aztecs",
       "The%20Edge%20of%20Destruction",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20show%20%22Tengen%20Toppa%20Gurren%20Lagann%22%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20character%20who%20force%20everyone%20to%20live%20underground%3F",
     correct_answer: "Lordgenome",
     incorrect_answers: ["Kingloname", "Lord%20Genome", "King%20Loname"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20real%20name%20of%20the%20famous%20spanish%20humorist%2C%20El%20Risitas%3F",
     correct_answer: "Juan%20Joya%20Borga",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Gabriel%20Garcia%20Marquez",
       "Jesus%20Quintero",
       "Ernesto%20Guevara",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20main%20character%20in%20%22The%20Flash%22%20TV%20series%3F",
     correct_answer: "Barry%20Allen",
     incorrect_answers: ["Oliver%20Queen", "Bart%20Allen", "Bruce%20Wayne"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20show%20is%20known%20for%20the%20songs%20%22You%20are%20a%20Pirate%22%2C%20%22Cooking%20by%20the%20Book%22%20and%20%22We%20Are%20Number%20One%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "LazyTown",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Sofia%20the%20First",
       "DuckTales",
       "Tom%20and%20Jerry",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "Who%20won%20Big%20Brother%202014%20UK%3F",
     correct_answer: "Helen%20Wood",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Christopher%20Hall",
       "Pauline%20Bennett",
       "Pavandeep%20%22Pav%22%20Paul",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20%22Breaking%20Bad%22%2C%20Walter%20White%20is%20a%20high%20school%20teacher%20diagnosed%20with%20which%20form%20of%20cancer%3F",
     correct_answer: "Lung%20Cancer",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Prostate%20Cancer",
       "Brain%20Cancer",
       "Testicular%20Cancer",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20these%20Disney%20shows%20is%20classified%20as%20an%20anime%3F",
     correct_answer: "Stitch%21",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Cory%20in%20the%20House",
       "The%20Emperor%27s%20New%20School",
       "Hannah%20Montana",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "When%20Donkey%20Kong%20died%20in%20the%20%22Donkey%20Kong%20Country%22%20episode%20%22It%27s%20a%20Wonderful%20Life%22%2C%20who%20was%20his%20guardian%20angel%3F",
     correct_answer: "Eddie%20the%20Mean%20Old%20Yeti",
     incorrect_answers: ["Kiddy%20Kong", "Diddy%20Kong", "King%20K.%20Rool"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "How%20many%20seasons%20did%20the%20Sci-Fi%20television%20show%20%22Stargate%20Atlantis%22%20have%3F",
     correct_answer: "5",
     incorrect_answers: ["10", "2", "7"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "How%20many%20seasons%20did%20the%20Sci-Fi%20television%20show%20%22Stargate%20Universe%22%20have%3F",
     correct_answer: "2",
     incorrect_answers: ["10", "5", "3"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20planet%20that%20the%20Doctor%20from%20television%20series%20%22Doctor%20Who%22%20comes%20from%3F",
     correct_answer: "Gallifrey",
     incorrect_answers: ["Sontar", "Skaro", "Mondas"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20TV%20show%20%22Mad%20Men%22%2C%20what%20was%20Donald%20Draper%27s%20birthname%3F",
     correct_answer: "Richard%20%22Dick%22%20Whitman",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Donald%20Draper",
       "John%20Ashbury",
       "Michael%20%22Mikey%22%20Wilhelm",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Who%20was%20the%20first%20ever%20actor%20to%20play%20%22The%20Doctor%22%20on%20%22Doctor%20Who%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "William%20Hartnell",
     incorrect_answers: ["David%20Tennant", "Peter%20Capaldi", "Tom%20Baker"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20NBC%20sitcom%20once%20saw%20two%20of%20its%20characters%20try%20to%20pitch%20NBC%20on%20a%20sitcom%20about%20nothing%3F",
     correct_answer: "Seinfeld",
     incorrect_answers: ["Frasier", "Becker", "Friends"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20won%20the%20first%20season%20of%20American%20Idol%20in%202002%3F",
     correct_answer: "Kelly%20Clarkson",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Justin%20Guarini",
       "Ruben%20Studdard",
       "Chris%20Daughtry",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "On%20the%20NBC%20show%20Community%2C%20whose%20catch-phrase%20was%20%22Pop%21%20Pop%21%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "Magnitude",
     incorrect_answers: ["Star%20Burns", "Leonard", "Senoir%20Chang"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "The%20HBO%20series%20%22Game%20of%20Thrones%22%20is%20based%20on%20which%20series%20of%20books%3F",
     correct_answer: "A%20Song%20of%20Ice%20and%20Fire",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "The%20Wheel%20of%20Time",
       "Harry%20Potter",
       "The%20Notebook",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20AMC%27s%20TV%20Series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%20what%20are%20%22Zombies%22%20referred%20to%20as%3F",
     correct_answer: "Walkers",
     incorrect_answers: ["Creepers", "Maggots", "Hell%20Pigs"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20teenage%20witch%20played%20by%20Melisa%20Joan%20Hart%20who%20lives%20with%20her%20witch%20aunts%20Hilda%20and%20Zelda%3F",
     correct_answer: "Sabrina",
     incorrect_answers: ["Hermione", "Dorothy", "Dahlia"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20which%20state%20of%20America%20was%20the%20Fresh%20Prince%20of%20Bel-Air%20born%20and%20raised%20in%3F",
     correct_answer: "Pennsylvania",
     incorrect_answers: ["Florida", "California", "New%20Jersey"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20show%20%22Dragonball%20Z%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cell%27s%20most%20powerful%20attack%3F",
     correct_answer: "Solar%20Kamehameha",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Super%20Kamehameha",
       "Cell%20Kamehameha",
       "Android%20Kamehameha",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20cartoon%20%27SpongeBob%20SquarePants%27%2C%20what%20did%20the%20acronym%20E.V.I.L%20stand%20for%3F",
     correct_answer: "Every%20Villain%20Is%20Lemons",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Every%20Villain%20Is%20Lemonade",
       "Every%20Villain%20Is%20Limes",
       "Each%20Villain%20Is%20Lemonade",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20awards%20do%20Matt%20Stone%20and%20Trey%20Parker%20NOT%20have%3F",
     correct_answer: "Oscar",
     incorrect_answers: ["Emmy", "Tony", "Grammy"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20show%20%22Futurama%22%20what%20is%20Fry%27s%20full%20name%3F",
     correct_answer: "Philip%20J.%20Fry",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Fry%20J.%20Philip",
       "Fry%20Rodr%C3%ADguez",
       "Fry%20Philip",
     ],
   },
 ];